[Check out our Resources section for free tax guides, forms, and more!](https://www.taxdefensenetwork.com/tax-guides/)

[855-476-6920](tel:855-476-6920) Se habla español

Menu

Tax Defense Network Privacy Policy
==================================

Arrow pointing down to indicate more content

Tax Defense Network (“Company”) is committed to keeping any and all personal information collected of those individuals who visit taxdefensenetwork.com (“Website”) and make use of our online facilities and services accurate, confidential, secure, and private. Our privacy policy has been designated and created to ensure those using our website are informed of our commitment to meet existing privacy standards.

THEREFORE, this Privacy Policy Agreement shall apply to Website and shall govern any and all data collection and usage thereof. Through the use of the Website, you are consenting to the following data and privacy procedures expressed within this agreement.

Collection of Information
-------------------------

The Company collects information about you in three ways_:_ (1) directly from you, (2) from our web server logs, and (3) through cookies. We primarily use the information to provide a personalized Internet experience that delivers the information, resources, and services that are most relevant and helpful to you. **We DO NOT share any information you provide with others** unless we are required to do so by law.

_User-supplied information:_ If you fill out the contact form on this website, we will ask you to provide some personal information, including name, phone, and email. If chat is available through the Website, you may be asked to provide information while participating in an online chat. Please do not submit any confidential, proprietary, or sensitive personally identifiable information. This includes Social Security numbers, driver’s license numbers, or other financial account information (sensitive information). If you submit any sensitive information, you do so at your own risk, and the Company will not be liable to you or responsible for the consequences of your submission.

The Company uses ActiveProspect’s TrustedForm Script to independently document your consent to be contacted. The TrustedForm Script is embedded on our website and collects the following information when you interact with the page(s) where the script is present: page URL, mouse movements and clicks, contact information inputted by you, a snapshot of the page, including IP address of your computer, time on the page, date and time that the TrustedForm Script was loaded, as well as the date and time of your interactions with the page, and HTTP headers from your browser. For more information about ActiveProspect’s data use and collection policies and practices, please review the ActiveProspect Privacy Policy, located at [https://activeprospect.com/privacy-policy/](https://activeprospect.com/privacy-policy/).

Use of Information Collected
----------------------------

Information you provide through the contact form or an online chat will be used so the Company may respond to your inquiries. We may also use the information you provide to communicate with you in the future. If you do not wish to receive such communications, you may opt out [(unsubscribe)](#) as described below.

_Cookies:_ In order to offer and provide a customized and personal service, our website may use cookies to store and help track information about you. Cookies are simply small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies to help remind us who you are and to help you navigate our site during your visits.

The use of cookies is relatively standard. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. However, if you prefer, you can set your browser to either notify you when you receive a cookie or to refuse to accept cookies. In some instances, certain features of many sites may not function properly if you don’t accept cookies.

How is Personal Information Protected?
--------------------------------------

We take various appropriate security measures to help protect your personal information from accidental loss and unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. We cannot guarantee, however, that unauthorized persons will always be unable to defeat our security measures.

### Do You Sell My Information?

**We DO NOT sell, rent, or lease mailing lists or other user data to others**, nor will we make your personal information available to any unaffiliated parties, except as follows:

* To agents, website vendors, and/or contractors who may use it on our behalf or in connection with their relationship with us.
* As required by law, in a matter of public safety or policy, as needed in connection with the transfer of our business assets (for example, if we are acquired by another firm or if we are liquidated during bankruptcy proceedings), or if we believe in good faith that sharing the data is necessary to protect our rights or property.

**Unsubscribe or Opt-Out**

You may opt out (unsubscribe) from future communications at any time by sending an email to [marketing@taxdefensenetwork.com](mailto:marketing@taxdefensenetwork.com) with the word “unsubscribe” in the subject line. You may also call, submit an [online contact form](#), or mail your request.

If you have additional questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, please contact us via the phone number, [contact form](#), or mailing address listed on this website. If our information practices change in a significant way, we will post the policy changes here.

State-Specific Terms
--------------------

### California Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of California, this section provides additional details about the personal information we collect about you and your rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) and California Privacy Rights Act (“CPRA”).

Subject to certain limitations, the CCPA and CPRA provide you the right to request:

* Access to details on the personal information we collect and/or sell (including how we use and disclose this information, to whom we may sell it);
* Deletion of your personal information;
* Correction of any inaccuracies in your personal information;
* To opt out of any “sale” or “sharing” of your personal information that may occur, including sensitive personal information; and
* To not be discriminated against for exercising any of the above rights.

If you would like to submit a request to exercise your California privacy rights, you may do so either by submitting a request through our [privacy rights form](https://www.taxdefensenetwork.com/privacy-request/) or by emailing [marketing@taxdefensenetwork.com](mailto:marketing@taxdefensenetwork.com) with your request. We will verify your request using information associated with your account, including your email. Further identification may be required. You may also designate an authorized agent to act on your behalf.

Please note that the Company may retain a record of your request to delete your personal information.

You have the right to opt out of the sale or sharing of your personal information, including for the purpose of cross-context behavioral advertising. To opt out of cross-context behavioral advertising, please activate the “Do Not Sell” option in your cookie preferences. To opt out of other kinds of sales or sharing, please submit our [opt-out form](https://www.taxdefensenetwork.com/opt-out/).

### Nevada Privacy Rights

Under Nevada law (SB 220), Nevada residents are permitted to opt out of the sale of certain kinds of personal information. The term “sale” as used in the foregoing sentence means the transfer of your personal information to third parties for monetary consideration so the third parties can then re-sell or license the sold personal information. If you are a Nevada resident and wish to obtain information about our compliance with Nevada law, or opt out of the sale of your personal information, please contact us at [marketing@taxdefensenetwork.com](mailto:marketing@taxdefensenetwork.com).

### Virginia Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of Virginia, this section provides information about your privacy rights under the Virginia Consumer Data Protection Act (“VCDPA”).

Subject to certain limitations, the VCDPA affords you the following rights:

* To confirm whether we are processing your personal information, and to access that personal information;
* To receive your personal information in a portable and readily usable format;
* To correct inaccuracies in your personal information;
* To delete your personal information;
* To opt out of the processing of your personal information for targeted advertising, sale to third parties, or profiling where there is a legal or similarly significant effect on you.

You may exercise these rights by visiting our [privacy rights form](https://www.taxdefensenetwork.com/privacy-request/), our [opt-out form](https://www.taxdefensenetwork.com/opt-out/), and by updating your cookie preferences. You can also email [marketing@taxdefensenetwork.com](mailto:marketing@taxdefensenetwork.com) for assistance with exercising your rights. If the Company declines your request for any reason, we will notify you. You can appeal this decision by contacting [marketing@taxdefensenetwork.com](mailto:marketing@taxdefensenetwork.com).

Changes to The Privacy Policy Agreement
---------------------------------------

The Company reserves the right to update and/or change the terms of our privacy policy (“Supplemental Policy”), and as such we will post those changes to this website policy page, so that our users and visitors are aware of the type of information we collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances we may disclose such information. If at any point in time Company decides to make use of any personally identifiable information on file in a manner vastly different from that which was stated with this information was initially collected, you shall be promptly notified by email. At that time, you shall have the option as to whether or not to permit the use of your information and will have the opportunity to opt-out. In addition, your continued use of our website following the posting of any updates or changes to our terms and conditions shall mean that you are in agreement and acceptance of such changes.

How to Contact Us
-----------------

If you have any questions or concerns regarding the Privacy Policy Agreement related to our website, please feel free to contact us at [marketing@taxdefensenetwork.com](mailto:marketing@taxdefensenetwork.com) or mail correspondence to:

Tax Defense Network  
Attn: Marketing Department  

9000 Southside Blvd., Bldg 100  
Suite 1900  
Jacksonville, FL 32256

Thank you for your interest in our tax relief services. At this time, we are unable to assist you. Please call [800-829-1040](tel:800-829-1040) to speak with the IRS and explore your options.

A Few Minutes Could Save You Thousands. Get Started Now!
--------------------------------------------------------

 First Name

 Last Name

 Email

 Phone

$0 - $7,499 $7,500 - $9,999 $10,000 - $19,999 $20,000 - $49,999 $50,000 - $99,999 $100,000+ I don't owe any taxes Tax Debt Amount

Please note that Tax Defense Network is a **private company** not affiliated with the IRS. If you decide to hire us to help with your tax relief problem(s), you will be charged for our services.

**Would you like to proceed with your free consultation?**

 Yes

 No

By submitting this form, you agree to our [Privacy Policy](https://www.taxdefensenetwork.com/privacy/) and [Terms of Use](https://www.taxdefensenetwork.com/terms-of-use/).

I agree to be contacted by Tax Defense Network, including calls, texts, and/or emails. Contact may be by automated dialing technology. I understand that my consent is not a condition or obligation to purchase any products or services. Message and data rates may apply. Message frequency varies. Reply STOP to cancel.

 Submit

Related Articles and Resources
------------------------------

[

### Exposing Tax Relief Scams and How to Avoid Them](https://www.taxdefensenetwork.com/blog/exposing-tax-relief-scams-and-how-to-avoid-them/)[

### Tax Season is Over. Can I Still Get Tax Relief?](https://www.taxdefensenetwork.com/blog/tax-season-is-over-can-i-still-get-tax-relief/)[

### IRS Negligence Penalty: What It Is & How To Fight It](https://www.taxdefensenetwork.com/blog/irs-negligence-penalty-what-it-is-how-to-fight-it/)

Tax Defense Network is a well-established tax resolution company that specializes in finding affordable solutions for state and federal tax problems. We are dedicated to helping our clients resolve their tax issues by providing exceptional customer service and transparent, affordable pricing. Since 2007, our team of licensed tax professionals has resolved more than $13 billion in tax debt.

9000 Southside Blvd., Bldg 100  
Suite 1900  
Jacksonville, FL 32256

The tax resolution companies referenced herein are not law firms nor are such representations being made. While they may employ attorneys, CPA’s and enrolled agents pursuant to IRS Regulation Circular 230, the use of the term ‘Tax Attorney’ is used as a general or generic term referencing attorneys seasoned in aspects of tax relief and collection work. They may or may not have a specialized degree in taxation or be individually licensed in your particular state.

Product name(s), logo(s), brands and other trademarks feature on referred to with this site(s) are the property of Tax Defense Network DBA MoneySolver. Information obtained through the site(s) are for advertising and/or educational purposes only. This site(s) is not endorsed or affiliated with any government or regulatory agencies.

© 2007-2024 Tax Defense Network, LLC. - [**Privacy**](https://www.taxdefensenetwork.com/privacy) | [**Terms of Use**](https://www.taxdefensenetwork.com/terms-of-use/) | [**Unsubscribe**](#)

-----------------------------------------------------------

--------------------------------------------------------------

------------------------------------------------------

-------------------------------------------------------

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------

-------------------------------------------------------------

-------------------------------------------------

X

Unsubscribe

 First Name

 Last Name

 Email

 Phone

Yes, please unsubscribe me from all communications.

 Submit

We use cookies to provide you with a great user experience. We also share that information with third parties for advertising and analytics. By continuing to use our site, you accept our use of cookies.  

Accept

Wait! Don’t go…
---------------

We know that tax debt is scary, but help is just a click away! Simply answer a few questions to help us better understand your situation. It only takes a few minutes, and you’ll get:

* A free, no-obligation tax consultation
* An overview of your tax resolution options
* Information on how to stop or prevent wage garnishment, liens, and levies
* Our free IRS Tax Relief Guide (no purchase required!)

or Call [855-476-6920](tel:855-476-6920) to speak with a tax specialist today!
